[Sumerian]: May all be well
[Ancient Greek]: Greetings to you, whoever you are.
We come in friendship to those who are friends.
[Portuguese]: Peace and happiness to everyone
[Cantonese]: How's everyone? Wish you peace, health and happiness
[Akkadian]: May all be very well
[Russian]: Greetings! I Welcome You!
[Thai]: Hello friends from farland.
We in this land have sent you warm greeting to you all
[Arabic]: Greetings to our friends in the stars. May time bring us together
[Romanian]: Regards to everyone
[French]: Hello to everyone
[Burmese]: Are you well?
[Hebrew]: Hello (literally "peace")
[Spanish]: Hello and greetings to everyone
[Indonesian]: Good night, ladies and gentlemen.
Goodbye and see you next time
[Quechua]: Hello to everybody from this Earth, in Quechua language
[Punjabi]: Welcome home. It is a pleasure to receive you
[Hittite]: Hail (literally "greetings")
[Bengali]: Hello! Let there be peace everywhere
[Latin]: Greetings to you, whoever you are; we have good
will towards you and bring peace across space
[Aramaic]: Hello (literally "peace")
[Dutch]: Dear/sincere greetings to everyone
[German]: Warm greetings to everyone
[Urdu]: Peace on you. We the inhabitants of
this earth send our greetings to you
[Vietnamese]: Sincere greetings to you
[Turkish]: Dear Turkish-speaking friends,
may the honors of the morning be upon your heads
[Japanese]: Hello. How are you?
[Hindi]: Greetings from the inhabitants of this world
[Welsh]: Good health to you now and forever
[Italian]: Many greetings and wishes
[Sinhala]: Wish You a Long Life.
[Zulu]: We greet you, great ones. We wish you longevity
[Sotho]: We greet you, O great ones
[Wu]: Best wishes to you all
[Armenian]: To all those who exist in the universe, greetings
[Korean]: Hello (literally "Are you peaceful?" or "Be peaceful")
[Polish]: Welcome, beings from beyond the world.
[Nepali]: Wishing you a peaceful future from the earthlings
[Mandarin Chinese]: How's everyone? We all very much wish
to meet you, if you're free please come and visit
[Ila]: We wish all of you well
[Swedish]: Greetings from a computer programmer in the
small university town of Ithaca on [the) planet Earth
[Nyanja]: How are all you people of other planets?
[Gujarati]: Greetings from a human being of the Earth.
Please contact
[Ukrainian]: We are sending greetings from our world,
wishing you happiness, health and many years
[Persian]: Greetings to the residents of far skies
[Serbian]: We wish you all the best, from our planet
[Oriya]: Greetings to the inhabitants of the
universe from the third planet Earth of the star Sun
[Ganda]: Greetings to all peoples of the universe.
God give you peace always
[Marathi]: Greetings. The people of the Earth send their
good wishes and hope you find good fortune in this life.
[Amoy]: Friends from space, how are you all?
Have you eaten yet? Come visit us if you have time
[Hungarian]: We are sending greetings in the Hungarian
language to all peace-loving beings on the Universe
[Telugu]: Greetings. Best wishes from Telugu-speaking people
[Czech]: Dear Friends, we wish you the best
[Kannada]: Greetings. On behalf of
Kannada-speaking people, "good wishes"
[Rajasthani]: Hello to everyone. We are happy here and you be happy there
[English]: Hello from the children of planet Earth